Meirunas Smitas

Portfolio: meru-portfolio.vercel.app Github: github.com/Meirunas LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/Meirunas

Personal Profile

I have gained over 3 years of full-time front-end experience in the pharma agency 28b. I developed multiple web/iOs solutions, internal tools and marketing materials for clients. In other similar roles I used web technologies. Prior to these roles I was studying MSc and BSc Computer Science at London Universities. Over 14 years in the IT environment I built a wide range of skills that could benefit your company.

SKILLS SUMMARY

Languages: HTML, SCSS, MJML, JavaScript, Handlebars, TypeScript, Python
 Frameworks & Libraries: React.js, Vue.js, Next.js, Redux, Node.js, Express.js

• Software: Adobe Cloud, Veeva, Salesforce, npm, MS Office, VS Code, Git, WordPress

• Databases: SQL, MySQL, MongoDB

• **Key Skills**: Self-motivation and Ability to take the initiative, Team working skills, Good communication skills, Able to work well under pressure

PROJECTS

- Portfolio: Building a responsive and dynamic single page application (SPA) portfolio (Personal Jul 2023 Now) GitHub
- Global & UK Digital Sales Aid (DSA): Involved in creating interactive and static slides. Reviewed Merge Requests by colleagues on (28b Dec 2022 Jun 2023) GitHub
- 28b & Client Veeva Approved Emails (VAE) Suite: Implemented different types of email templates serving healthcare purposes (28b Oct Nov 2022) GitHub
- HADEA Website: Created responsive and dynamic charity website (HADEA Aug 2019 Apr 2020) GitHub
- Travel & Explore Now: Built a full-stack travelling e-commerce website (Final year undergraduate project Sep 2017 Jun 2018) GitLab

EXPERIENCE

Iron Mountain

Hoddesdon

Digital Solutions Operative

Jun 2024 - Present

Email: meirunas.smi@icloud.com

Mobile: 07727 825042

- Processing documents and data entry
- o Inputting client data on to Iron Mountain databases
- $\circ\,$ Sensitivity checking documentation
- o Scanning documents
- o Carrying out all ad-hoc administrative and site support duties as requested
- $\circ\,$ Carrying out manual handling tasks in order to retrieve data
- $\circ~$ Dealing with confidential/top secret documents in a professional manner at data centre

Targech
Vue.js Developer

Remote
Dec 2023 - Mar 2024

- o Analysing existing programs for modification purposes
- $\circ\,$ Researching and designing new software systems, websites, programs and applications
- $\circ~$ Writing and implementing, clean, scalable code
- o Troubleshooting and debugging code
- o Verifying and deploying software systems
- \circ Evaluating user feedback
- Recommending and executing program improvements
- o Creating UI for recruitment website and testing
- o Configuring and implementing authentication system and payment processing gateway and API

28b
Junior Developer

Mar 2020 - Jun 2023

- o Investigating and resolving production issues
- Responding to escalated customer questions from the Support team
- o Performing root-cause analysis for production errors
- o Developing software to automate operational needs
- Implementing Digital Sales Aids for iOS/Web platforms using the Veeva and IQVIA APIs that helped clients with their sales
- o Developing responsive emails on CRM, Salesforce and iPad
- o Implementing internal tools that helped increase the software quality and accelerated the delivery process
- Using code standard guidelines and best engineering practices, such as code reviews, Git branching strategy and CI/CD
- Improving internal documentation (Company Wiki)

EDUCATION

Queen Mary University PGC in Computer Science 2018 University of Westminster BSc Computer Science (1st) 2018 Conel College (Pearson) BTEC Level 2, 3 and 4 in IT and Computing and Systems Development) 2011/2014

Hobbies & Interests

I enjoy travelling and exercising. I like playing games and watching movies.

References

References available on request.